<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourApp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">destination</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">festival</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tribe</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">COUNTRY</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="maasai">MAASAI MARA</string>
    <string name="ghana_">ASHANTIS</string>
    <string name="uganda">Uganda</string>
    <string name="kampala_">Uganda officially the Republic of Uganda is a landlocked country (except for bordering a lake) in East-Central Africa.
        It is bordered to the east by Kenya, to the north by South Sudan, to the west by the Democratic Republic of the Congo, to the south-west by Rwanda, and to the south by Tanzania. The southern part of the country includes a substantial portion of Lake Victoria, shared with Kenya and Tanzania.
        Uganda is in the African Great Lakes region. Uganda also lies within the Nile basin, and has a varied but generally a modified equatorial climate.

Uganda takes its name from the Buganda kingdom, which encompasses a large portion of the south of the country, including the capital Kampala. The people of Uganda were hunter-gatherers until 1,700 to 2,300 years ago, when Bantu-speaking populations migrated to the southern parts of the country</string>
    <string name="kenya_">Maasai Mara (Masai Mara) is situated in south-west Kenya and it is one of Africa’s Greatest Wildlife Reserves
    \n  The Maasai Mara is an all year round destination with the big cats, and all the big game still in the Maasai Mara Ecosystem.</string>
    <string name="Nigeria_">NIGERIA</string>
    <string name="eyo_festival">EYO FESTIVAL \n\nThe Eyo Festival, otherwise known as the Adamu Orisha Play, is a Yoruba festival unique to Lagos, Nigeria.The word "Eyo" also refers to the costumed dancers, known as the masquerades that come out during the festival.\n
     Back in the days, The Eyo festival is held to escort the soul of a departed Lagos King or Chief and to usher in a new king.</string>
    <string name="ashanti_people">Ashanti also known as Asante are an ethnic group native to the Ashanti Region of modern-day Ghana.\n The people of ashanti speak the Asante dialect of Twi. Ashanti culture celebrates Adae, Adae Kese, Akwasidae, Awukudae and Ashanti Yam festival
    \n The Ashanti state strongly resisted attempts by Europeans, mainly the British, to conquer them.
        \The Ashanti limited British influence in the Ashanti region, as Britain annexed neighbouring areas.\n
        The Ashanti were described as a fierce organized people whose king "can bring 200,000 men into the field and whose warriors are evidently not cowed by Sniper riflesand 7-pounder guns"</string>
    <string name="continent">africa</string>
    <string name="mainImage">mainImage</string>
</resources>
